Wanna go watch the boys play soccer?
Hmm, should we?
Boys
Girls
Baseball
Soccer
Volleyball
Basketball
Ball Sports Tournament
Assignments
Chiba
Nishida
Kobayashi
Ueda
Saitou
Funazawa
Fusube
Yamana
Saitou
Inuzuka
Nakajo
Niwano
Izumi
Tanaka
Saeki
Hisano
Minami
Numakoshi
Shikimori
Takeda
Taneda
Koyama
Nakahashi
Nekozaki
Nagumo
Oohara
Tsunozaki
Kurisu
Morita
Hashioka
Hachimitsu
Emoto
Tokuda
Hiraana
Satou
Hikida
Oh, the girls are doing
volleyball and basketball, huh?
Looks like you and I are up for soccer.
Yeah, looks like it.
Today is our ball sports tournament.
If we're gonna do this,
we wanna win, right?
Yeah!
And I hope no one gets hurt this time.
You'd better be especially careful.
I appreciate the concern.
Izumi-san!
The girls' volleyball game starts 11:35.
What time is the boys' soccer game?
I haven't checked yet.
Her hair looks so cute today!
Isn't playing gonna be hard
with your hair like that?
W-Well, a little...
We match. It's nice, right?
How do you figure?
It makes us feel connected,
it motivates us, and it gets our spirits up!
Hachimitsu, you look so good!
Take it off.
Excuse me.
I'm gonna hit the can.
Oh!
The times are posted right here.
Oh, you're right.
It's pretty clear that I won't be of
much use in this ball sports tournament.
In which case...
Here!
Eep!
I'll focus on supporting Shikimori-san
to make myself look good!
Wait a minute...
Does supporting someone make you look good?
Well, whatever!
Uh... Oh, here we are.
Girls
Basketball
Soccer
Volleyball
Boys
They're at the same time!
Looks like we won't be able
to cheer each other on today.
Our opponent in the first match
is the favorite to win, too.
Really?
Volleyball
Volleyball Ace
One Volleyball Club Member
Basketball
Neko is in the volleyball club,
and she says they've got
the ace on their team.
It won't be easy for our class to win.
Shikimori-san!
Huh?!
Even if we're apart, I'll be
cheering you on the whole time!
I'll send you my good vibes now!
You can do it! Don't get hurt! Hnngh!
I'll...
I'll do my best.
Shikimori's Not Just a Cutie
Shikimori's
Not
Just
a
Cutie
Shikimori's
Not
Just
a
Cutie
Shikimori's
Not Just a Cutie
Amusement Park
Shikimori-san might like it??
Get a reservation!!!
Get gifts for the family
Eat this!!
Inuzuka-kun
Keep warm and go to bed early!!
Inuzuka-kun!!
Please Help
I'm going to an amusement park with
Shikimori-san next week. Suggestions...?
#02  Wind and Clouds, Ball Sports Tournament!
You've got this!
Focus!
You can do it!
Good luck!
Get 'em!
Go for it!
You can do it!
Ow...
Izumi-san...
Man, is he okay?
His bad luck's rearing
its head from the get-go.
Izumi-san sent me good vibes
so I wouldn't get hurt...
You can do it! Don't get hurt! Hnngh!
Say what?
All right!
Ack! Yeowch!
Maybe it worked. Coulda been way worse.
Get back! Get back!
Ouch...
Izumi-san!
Shikimori-san?
The ball's coming at you!
It's coming!
Pay attention!
Was that a "good luck"?
Izumi!
That had to hurt...
Micchon?
The volleyball game's gonna start!
Are you okay?
Sorry! You go on ahead!
Oh, man...
You okay?
Jeez, she's so overprotective.
Nurse's Office
Are you all right, Izumi-san?
You don't feel ill, do you?
Do you want some water?
Nah, I'm okay.
What about you? Will you make
it to your volleyball game?
I still have some time.
Still, I can't believe the ball hit you
right smack in the face like that...
Don't remind me. I looked so dumb.
It wasn't bad luck this time.
It was just clumsiness.
Do you have to be so frank?!
I made her worry again. I'm pathetic.
Honestly...
You have such pretty hair, Izumi-san.
R-Really?!
This scar... I didn't know
you had such a big scar here.
That tickles...
I suffered some pretty
bad injuries in the past.
I have scars all over the place.
I think this was from the time
a truck ran into our house.
C R A S H
I swear, nothing you say
will ever surprise me again!
I really...
do worry about you a lot.
So please stay by my side
as much as possible, okay?
R-Really, I'm fine...
Well, I should head back.
I can...
I can protect you, too, Shikimori-san.
I don't think I'll head back after all.
Huh?!
But the game will start without you!
Then...
Maybe I'll hide in here.
Wha— Buh— Wai—
Gotcha.
I was just kidding!
Don't tease me!
Well, I'll see you later.
I came on too strong...
You can do it!
Good luck!
That's it!
Nice shot!
Good game!
Goin' all out, huh?
I am... not...
Uh, you're wheezing pretty hard, though.
Well, we'll win the volleyball
game! Cheer for us!
Sure.
Oh, she's here!
I'm rooting for you, Kamiya-senpai!
Me, too!
Please, take this!
And this!
Thanks.
Well, bye now!
Bye!
As popular as ever, huh, Kamiya?
Yeah, I guess they're expecting a lot of me.
We're not gonna lose this match!
Right.
Neko!
Micchon, you're finally here.
Sorry! Did it start yet?
Just about to.
Huh?
Oh, that's the volleyball ace.
Ah...
Kamiya-senpai!
Go get 'em!
I knew she was good.
That was amazing!
She's quite strong.
Team
1st Half
2nd Half
Overtime
Good game!
Wanna catch the girls' volleyball game?
It's over... Our summer is over...
Rejoined During Stoppage Time
It hasn't even started yet. It's still spring.
What the heck happened?
Anyway, you ended up getting
hurt after all, huh?
Yeah, but thankfully it wasn't serious.
True!
I wonder if the girls are still playing.
Wanna go?
Yeah.
Keep it up!
You can do it!
That's the way!
Let's see your spirit!
Shikimori! Nekozaki!
Let's see your spirit! Your spirit!
Let's watch from above.
Don't trip on the way up.
Right.
You got it! You got it!
Get the next one!
You can do it!
Neko! Are you okay?
Damn, she's taking this seriously.
Man, they're on fire!
And they're still on the first round!
Go for it! Get 'em!
Hachimitsu!
You came at the perfect time.
Hey, you're still wearing that?
Shut it.
Looks like an exciting game.
It's still going on?
There she goes!
Damn, she's good! How many
spikes has she received now?
Who is that?!
Shikimori's kind of awesome.
Yep.
Wait... our class is still losing?
You can do it!
Shikimori-san!
One more point!
You can get it!
Looks like your bae came to cheer for you.
Well, I can't lose now.
Who is that hot guy?
Dude, chill. That's your girlfriend.
Is that Kamiya-san?
You know her?
Yeah, sort of.
That was awesome!
Nice one!
You've got this!
All right! They tied it up!
Keep it up!
You can do it!
Go, Shikimori!
Micchon!
Awesome!
That was amazing!
They won...
For real?!
Not bad.
Micchon!
Neko... We did it!
Yeah!
What's wrong?
Oh, nothing.
Shikimori-san!
You were amazing, Shikimori-san!
I knew you could do it!
Congratulations!
Th-Thank you...
Good game.
I bet you can win the next one, too!
Heck yeah! We gotta do this now!
I'll be cheering you on with all I've got!
I-I'll do my best!
Great tournament, everyone!
Nekozaki, you were awesome!
I was impressed.
Shikimori-san was amazing, too!
Celebrate ♥ 2-4
Volleyball Victory!!
Congratulations
I think I cried a little!
Let's party!
Hey, why don't we do karaoke? I love singing!
You really were amazing, Shikimori-san.
Oh, no... I only did so well
because you were cheering for me.
Shikimori-san, I envy how athletic you are.
Really?
Blocked a newspaper
without looking
You constantly radiate athleticism.
I don't really...
You're so cute.
Meanwhile, I got knocked out
of the game first thing.
I know you did your best.
I think you look so cool when
you're trying your hardest.
Th-Thanks...
Excuse me! Can I get a picture with you?
Please tell me your name!
Can I shake your hand?
Who's he? Your boyfriend?
He's kinda cute.
He is!
So cute...
My girlfriend has become the school hero.
A Few Days Later
You look so cool again today!
Shikimori-senpai! Would you
please eat lunch with me?
Uh, well...
Do you make your own lunches?
Um...
Is there anyone you eat with?
Well...
C-Can I shake your hand?
Me, too!
No fair! I want to shake your hand, too!
Shikimori's become a real celebrity
since the ball sports tournament.
And look at them.
Okay, get in line.
Each one of you will have
ten seconds to shake her hand.
I want an instant photo, please!
An instant photo...? Y-You really need that?
Nekozaki's in on it, too?
It's been crazy since they won, huh?
I bet this is nothing but a
pain in the ass for you, though.
What should I do?
I can't even get near Shikimori-san.
Here we go!
Yeah, when she has to be so nice and
polite to each one of those fangirls...
She's everyone's Shikimori-san now.
I guess that's just how it is.
We live in different worlds.
Stop talking like an obsessive fan.
Izumi!
Get back!
Inuzuka-kun!
That sudden stroke of bad luck...
I'm sorry, Inuzuka-kun!
This was probably my fault!
Yeah, probably...
That was scary.
What happened? A ball flew in the window?
E-Excuse me... I need to get through!
Should we call the teacher?
Please, let me through!
Are you okay?
Th-Thanks...
Senpai?
There it is!
She's gorgeous when she's angry!
I can't tell if her eyes are saying "hands off"
or "you should've protected him."
I'm scared...
I'm not sure what any of that
meant, but are you okay?
Today was kind of exhausting.
I really am hopeless without Shikimori-san.
Like when that bucket fell from the sky...
Ruthless
Vice Principal
And when I almost walked
into the vice principal...
You're on your own getting home.
I've caused a lot of trouble
for Inuzuka-kun, too.
But all that aside,
Shikimori-san's gotten so popular...
She really is amazing.
She gets more and more famous every
time there's any kind of event.
But...
I wanted to keep her cool side all to myself.
I close my eyes for one second,
and this is what happens!
Oh, no...
Hey.
Who said you could go home alone?
Wh-Wh-What are you doing here?!
You're the one who left on your own.
Well, I mean...
You're basically a celebrity.
I figured I shouldn't get in the way.
What are you saying?
You know you're the only one
I want to walk home with.
You planned to walk home with
Inuzuka-kun anyway, didn't you?
Huh?
Well, you've been with
him all the time lately!
More than with me!
Why are you laughing?
Sorry. It's not what you're thinking.
I was going to wait for you at the entrance.
Because I've been missing you, too.
I-If that's what this was about,
you should have said so sooner.
Sorry.
Ready to go?
Yeah.
SEE YOU~